You lift straight up, and it comes up.
你把它拿起来 它就跟着起来了
But...
但是
Oh!
哦
Towards the camera.
试试相机这边
Aye! Pah!
雾草
It's stressful every time!
感觉每次都十分紧张
It looks like it's gonna go.
它看起来像会倒下
You feel like it's gonna...
你感觉它会
But it isn't gonna go.
但是它没有耶
What if I...
那这样呢
Whoooooo!
喔噢
Got me feeling a little nilly-willy.
弄得我有些懵了
That's a lot of ...
这可有很多
Do I slap it?
我拍了哈
我真拍了哈
Eraaaa!
我要发功啦
Bwaa
雾草​
Wow!
哇
What?
天哪
How do I not have this already?
我怎么就没有它呢
How does everyone not have this?
为什么不每个人都拥有一个
I mean, if you could
我是说 你可以
forget about the splash coming out the top,
忽略从顶上洒出来
which you could...
可以像这样
I'm spl...
我拍
Whoa man, my life is changed.
天啊 我的三观都被碾压了
What about picking it up?
那把它拿起来 怎么样
Let's say I want to take a drink.
其实是我渴了
What?
什么